[{"answer": "I do not, Piers, but I do believe that we may reach a point where the markets have to tell us to come through an agreement and that would be of course when we start defaulting on our debts.", "docId": "131007pmt", "aSentId": 20, "question": "Do you have the answer?", "qSentId": 19}, {"answer": "To be honest, I don't know, because I say it with respect to those individuals who say defund or nothing else, although they have changed their message somewhat it used to be just absolute defunding, now apparently it's already if you just address certain portions of ObamaCare, but look there was a lot of republican members of congress who campaigned in 2010 and said, \"You send me there, I'll do everything in my power to defund ObamaCare.\"", "docId": "131007pmt", "aSentId": 30, "question": "How do you bring the two together and get some kind of common sense?", "qSentId": 29}, {"answer": "I think it's very difficult for me to say because I'm a great admirer of the speaker and it's very tough given the divisions within his conference.", "docId": "131007pmt", "aSentId": 39, "question": "If you were Speaker Boehner, what would you do now to try and get through this?", "qSentId": 38}, {"answer": "Well, I would -- If were the president, I look at my own polls.", "docId": "131007pmt", "aSentId": 47, "question": "At what point does that political stunt which gets perfectly understandable becomes against the national interest particularly with the debt ceiling coming up so fast?", "qSentId": 46}, {"answer": "Because it's on both sides.", "docId": "131007pmt", "aSentId": 68, "question": "But why should the conversation start with a metaphorical gun to his head?", "qSentId": 67}, {"answer": "Well, the point is staying on both houses.", "docId": "131007pmt", "aSentId": 102, "question": "INGRICH: Well, Barack Obama ain't no Bill Clinton, so what's the point?", "qSentId": 101}, {"answer": "All right.", "docId": "131007pmt", "aSentId": 142, "question": "I don't know (inaudible), will you?", "qSentId": 141}, {"answer": "I'm real good.", "docId": "131007pmt", "aSentId": 156, "question": "How are you?", "qSentId": 155}, {"answer": "Yeah, you love animals that's why we're here.", "docId": "131007pmt", "aSentId": 169, "question": "I could be any animal?", "qSentId": 168}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "131007pmt", "aSentId": 172, "question": "An elephant?", "qSentId": 171}, {"answer": "They have 105,000 muscles in their trunk.", "docId": "131007pmt", "aSentId": 174, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 173}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "131007pmt", "aSentId": 176, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 175}, {"answer": "And they're big and they last a long time.", "docId": "131007pmt", "aSentId": 181, "question": "You want 105,000 muscles in your trunk?", "qSentId": 180}, {"answer": "Well, no actually.", "docId": "131007pmt", "aSentId": 190, "question": "So you're basically basing -- and this is based on Newt, right?", "qSentId": 189}, {"answer": "That was the decisive moment, Pier.", "docId": "131007pmt", "aSentId": 199, "question": "Have you found that British person who said that?", "qSentId": 198}, {"answer": "Great question.", "docId": "131007pmt", "aSentId": 206, "question": "What is your most common argument at home?", "qSentId": 205}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "131007pmt", "aSentId": 211, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 210}, {"answer": "I think so.", "docId": "131007pmt", "aSentId": 219, "question": "The public are sick and tired of this, aren't they?", "qSentId": 218}, {"answer": "Well, you have to call Van Jones (ph) to come around and ...", "docId": "131007pmt", "aSentId": 228, "question": "Dispute?", "qSentId": 227}, {"answer": "I look at it this way.", "docId": "131007pmt", "aSentId": 277, "question": "And the moment I heard that, I thought, \"This is the guy,\" because if you can get out of a straitjacket, we can get out of this shutdown, right?", "qSentId": 276}, {"answer": "I'm going to put you in a straitjacket.", "docId": "131007pmt", "aSentId": 294, "question": "And you are going to come back with me with a straitjacket, a bit later, right?", "qSentId": 293}, {"answer": "Yes, it's on Spike.", "docId": "131007pmt", "aSentId": 299, "question": "Very quickly, you got a new show, Believe?", "qSentId": 298}, {"answer": "Yes, you know, you two do similar jobs that just make the economy sense for you to go, Dan (ph).", "docId": "131007pmt", "aSentId": 322, "question": "Ma'am?", "qSentId": 321}, {"answer": "Well, you must think you're either a soothsayer or you're just so long in the tooth in this Washington game.", "docId": "131007pmt", "aSentId": 335, "question": "Good evening, how are you?", "qSentId": 334}, {"answer": "Well, I must say Armando Iannucci who said -- really brilliant creative guy behind writing Veep, has this uncanny ability, particularly, since he is after all British, to predict, but you may have this ability too.", "docId": "131007pmt", "aSentId": 338, "question": "I mean what do you make and what's going on now, particularly, as you've lampooned this so successfully?", "qSentId": 337}, {"answer": "No, I don't think there's any parallel to this, you know, Secretary (inaudible), I thought, got something slightly off in the earlier segment when he said that, \"There was no particular law involved in the previous conflict in the Gingrich-Clinton standoff because there was one similarity, it was about -- the budget was about Medicare.", "docId": "131007pmt", "aSentId": 344, "question": "Can you remember one that has been (inaudible) hot over one side trying to dismantle and establish law?", "qSentId": 343}, {"answer": "Well, I think you're right.", "docId": "131007pmt", "aSentId": 352, "question": "The sense -- because, you know, midterms coming up, and you have the big election in 2016, it can't be helpful, can it, the chances of doing one and either of those two elections if they are seen to be absolutely ideologically at each other's throats?", "qSentId": 351}, {"answer": "There's nothing that you can't parity and we know it from shows not just like Veep in Saturday Night Live, but so many shows in American television.", "docId": "131007pmt", "aSentId": 395, "question": "ORGAN: Is there anything you couldn't parity, Frank?", "qSentId": 394}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "131007pmt", "aSentId": 409, "question": "You think they've ever going to grow up in Washington?", "qSentId": 408}, {"answer": "Well, Piers, Edwin is clearly a victim.", "docId": "131007pmt", "aSentId": 430, "question": "And why do you believe the real victim may, will be, Edwin and not as many people think Alexian Lien who was of course the driver of the SUV?", "qSentId": 429}, {"answer": "He's out of his comma.", "docId": "131007pmt", "aSentId": 445, "question": "What's his condition at the moment?", "qSentId": 444}, {"answer": "I mean I wasn't there.", "docId": "131007pmt", "aSentId": 454, "question": "What is your view about where blames should lie here?", "qSentId": 453}, {"answer": "I think, I would have stopped and I would have tried to get the information for the insurance.", "docId": "131007pmt", "aSentId": 515, "question": "What would you want to do?", "qSentId": 514}, {"answer": "They hadn't done anything.", "docId": "131007pmt", "aSentId": 543, "question": "What do you think, Dayana?", "qSentId": 542}, {"answer": "Enough not to...", "docId": "131007pmt", "aSentId": 545, "question": "How many bikers do you see in this video, 3 -- 400, 500 bikers or 20?", "qSentId": 544}, {"answer": "Because I would be very concerned...", "docId": "131007pmt", "aSentId": 550, "question": "Why would you be scared?", "qSentId": 549}, {"answer": "And that this is my point.", "docId": "131007pmt", "aSentId": 557, "question": "Do we have evidence of that?", "qSentId": 556}, {"answer": "All right.", "docId": "131007pmt", "aSentId": 559, "question": "Is there evidence to that?", "qSentId": 558}, {"answer": "I see hundreds of bikes.", "docId": "131007pmt", "aSentId": 569, "question": "Do you see them already banging and hitting this vehicle before?", "qSentId": 568}, {"answer": "(Inaudible).", "docId": "131007pmt", "aSentId": 576, "question": "But dozens -- I mean, how many it will take to be scary?", "qSentId": 575}, {"answer": "I will say that I'm going to leave you like the couple moments leaving us.", "docId": "131007pmt", "aSentId": 604, "question": "And anyway, how are you Criss Angel?", "qSentId": 603}]